go4wallpapers.com 2017-02-21

# Go4wallpapers,Get latest Wallpapers Privacy Policy

Go4wallpapers.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Throughout the cyberspace we want to contribute towards providing a safe and secure environment, safe information gathering and dissemination practices for all our sites. This policy applies only to go4wallpapers.com which carry the go4wallpapers.com brand and not to other companies or organisations' websites to which we link.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Information Gathering And Usage  
**1\. Feedback**

Our site's feedback form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age etc ).

We use customer contact information from the feedback form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitors' experience at our site, showing them the content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.

Users may opt out of receiving future mailings; by sending us an e-mail.

**2\. Contests**  
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), financial information (income bracket), and demographic information (like their zip code, age or income level).

We use contact data from our contestant to send information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The users' contact information is also used by us to contact the visitor when necessary, primarily to announce new contests and features of the site.

A user may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest organizer ( the website ) or the sponsor, in which the user identity is divulged to the third party, as long as the user gives hi s/her consent.

Users may opt out of receiving future mailings; by sending us an e-mail.

**3\. Electronic Newsletter**  
The site offers a free electronic newsletter to its users. We gather the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by using the link provided in every newsletter.

**4\. Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. go4wallpapers.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above) and for the personalisation feature.

If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any go4wallpapers.com.

**5\. Choice/Opt Out policy**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.  
**  
6\. Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this website contact please [click here](http://www.go4wallpapers.com/contactus.html)
